kesinenitravels.com 2015-12-07

# Kesineni® Travels Online Bus Booking and Ticket Reservation Service | Kesineni®

**Sharing of Personal Information**

Kesineni will never sell your personal or financial information to any third party. Your personal or financial information, used for the following purposes: 

• Credit card verification and fraud detection purposes as part of your ticket purchase. 

• Legal disclosure to a governmental agency, law enforcement authority or court as required by law in the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary or advisable. 

**Personal Information Collected For Processing Transactions**

Kesineni collects personal information (name, address, phone number, etc.) to process transactions. An e-mail address for an online purchase is optional; however, your e-mail address is required if you would like a copy of your confirmation statement e-mailed to you. 

**On-line Collection of Personal Information**

Kesineni’s website is not directed at children under the age of thirteen, and accordingly, Kesineni does not intentionally collect any personal information from anyone under age thirteen. 

**Non-Personal Information Collected  
**   
• **IP Addresses**   
An Internet protocol ("IP") address is a numeric code, for example, "152.163.207.197." This code is used to communicate between your Internet service provider and the World Wide Web. The IP address does not identify you individually. Kesineni logs inbound IP addresses to administer the Web site and to compile aggregate information on site traffic for internal use.

• **Cookies**   
Cookies are small computer files written to your computer when you visit Web sites. You have the option of setting your browser to refuse Cookies. To utilize all promotional offers and discounts on Kesinenitravels.com you need to allow temporary "session cookies" that will go away when your browser is closed. No personal or credit card information is collected by any Kesineni related Cookies. your Internet service provider and the World Wide Web. The IP address does not identify you individually. Kesineni logs inbound IP addresses to administer our Web site and to compile aggregate information on site traffic for internal use. 

Kesineni also works with on-line advertising agencies to sell Kesineni’s services. These agencies use Cookies to track which Kesineni ads you have seen and the amounts you spend on Kesinenitravels.com so that we may effectively market to consumers. 

**Cancellation of service**

• Kesineni may cancel a service without any prior notice in case of circumstances beyond its control. In such circumstances Kesineni shall either reschedule the journey for travel on the next Kesineni service in the same sector, Subject to availability without any extra charge based on the passenger’s conveyance or enable a full refund of the ticket as paid by the passenger and shall be under no further liability to the passenger. The passenger will be required to collect the refund from the point of purchase. 

**Security  
**   
Kesineni takes reasonable procedures to avoid your personal and credit card information from misuse or unauthorized disclosure. The credit card information will be accepted on the concerned bank's payment gateway and is not at Kesineni’s website or server in any manner. 

All credit card information will be gathered on HDFC Bank payment gateway which uses encryption software from VeriSign, the industry leader in secure site software technologies to protect your information. 

Look for the gold key (Internet Explorer) or lock (Netscape) as well as the "s" after "http" in the address line of your browser. These signs mean the information sent from your computer to Kesinenitravels.com is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

**Consent**

Your use of Kesineni's Web site, services and participation in our marketing programs is your express consent to Kesineni to use your personal information as described above. We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy from time to time, and for this reason, we encourage you to review the policy posted at www.kesinenitravels.com periodically. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about the use of your personal information or would like to correct or amend any personal information we maintain about you, please feel free to contact us at [info@kesinenitravels.com.](mailto:info@kesinenitravels.com)
